var distractor = [
  {
    "Problem": "3 + 4",
    "Answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "Problem": "1+ 5",
    "Answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "Problem": "8 + 1",
    "Answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "Problem": "13 - 8",
    "Answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "Problem": "45 - 42",
    "Answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "Problem": "15 - 7",
    "Answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "Problem": "20 - 18",
    "Answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "Problem": "2 + 2",
    "Answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "Problem": "4 - 3",
    "Answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "Problem": "16 - 9",
    "Answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "Problem": "7 - 1",
    "Answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "Problem": "35 - 35",
    "Answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "Problem": "258 - 249",
    "Answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "Problem": "-23 + 31",
    "Answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "Problem": "-11 + 14",
    "Answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "Problem": "87-79",
    "Answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "Problem": "43 - 34",
    "Answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "Problem": "-7 + 13",
    "Answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "Problem": "98 - 93",
    "Answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "Problem": "-2 + 3",
    "Answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "Problem": "-31 + 33",
    "Answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "Problem": "368 - 366",
    "Answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "Problem": "-15 + 18",
    "Answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "Problem": "999-994",
    "Answer": "5"
  }
]
